militarybenefits.info 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy

**  Privacy Policy – MilitaryBenefits.info**

Updated: August 14, 2017

BY ACCESSING THIS WEBSITE MilitaryBenefits.info.  YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

This website is owned and operated by Military Benefits. We at Military Benefits (referred to as “Company.”, “we”, “us”, or “our”) recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of certain information (“information”) collected about our customers and prospective customers (referred to as “customers”, “you”, “visitors” or “your”). This privacy statement, effective December 7th, 2011 discloses the privacy practices our collection, use, and disclosure of information.

Military Benefits (Company) respects your right to privacy and has committed to protecting your privacy. The continued use of our website and your submission of any information to us indicate that you have read, understand and agree to our Privacy Policy. If you are not in agreement with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please use or access the MilitaryBenefits.info website.

This policy describes the information collection, use, and dissemination practices of MilitaryBenefits.info.  This Privacy Policy indicates what information we may obtain in our normal business operations, how we may share it, what may happen to the information and how you can inform us of your preferences.

**Information Collected on this Website.**

**Visitors.** No personally-identifiable information is collected on MilitaryBenefits.info from Visitors that browse the site for information.

As with most web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We do allow third-party companies to collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or a third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org.

Personally Identifiable Information. We may collect information that can be used to identify you (“Personally Identifiable Information”). We only collect Personally Identifiable Information when you specifically provide it to us. For example, in connection with your use of certain features of the Websites you may be asked to provide certain information including your name and email address in order to receive a newsletter.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information to fulfill your requests, respond to your inquiries and provide other services, and to alert you to information, offers, or publications in which we think you may be interested. The emails that we send contain links that enable you to “unsubscribe” from such mailings. We do not sell Personally Identifiable Information or other information you make available or share such information with third parties, except as described below.

From time to time, we may partner with unaffiliated companies or individuals for market research, product development or similar purposes.  We also may subcontract with other companies and individuals to do work on our behalf; they may be provided with access to Personally Identifiable and Non-Personally Identifiable Information, but only as needed to perform their functions.

We may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties in connection with a corporate transaction where all or a portion of our business (e.g., a portion that includes our customer lists) is sold or transferred. We also may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information if disclosure is required by law or as part of a lawsuit or government investigation or proceeding, or in order to permit us to exercise or preserve our legal rights or take action regarding potentially illegal activities or to protect the safety of any person.

**No Information is knowingly Collected from Children under the age of 13  **

MilitaryBenefits.info is a general audience website and is intended to be used by adults. We do not knowingly solicit, collect, or attract personal information from or about children. MilitaryBenefits.info is not intended for children and the we do not want to collect any personally identifiable information from Users who are under the age of 13. The safety of children is very important to the MilitaryBenefits.info and we strongly recommends that parents review this Privacy Policy and understand its terms and conditions, so that this site is used only by persons age 13 and over.

We use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit MilitaryBenefits.info. Third party advertising companies use information about your visits to MilitaryBenefits.info. In the course of our advertisements being served to you, these companies may place or recognize their own unique third-party cookies on your browser. In addition, we may use Web beacons, provided by some of our third-party advertising companies, to help manage our online advertising. These Web beacons allow us to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits this site and to learn which banner ads bring users to our website.

  * a. **Cookies.** Cookies are small chunks of data created by a web server, delivered through a web browser, and stored on your computer. They provide a means for websites that you visit to keep track of your online patterns and preferences, as well as identify you as a return visitor. Cookies make the personalization of your web experiences possible, so that you do not need to re-enter your information from scratch upon each visit to a given website. [Individuals who use MilitaryBenefits.info need to accept cookies in order to use all of the features and functionality of the site.
  * b. **Web Beacons.** A web beacon is programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page, but can also be used to transfer an individual’s unique user identification (often in the form of a cookie) to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows us to track certain websites an individual visits online. Web beacons are used to determine products or services an individual may be interested in, and to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes.
  * d. **IP Address.** We collect your IP (Internet Protocol) address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer MilitaryBenefits.info. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. Your IP address is also used to help identify you during a particular session and to gather broad demographic data

Our website may contain affiliate marketing links, which means we may get paid commission on sales of those products or services we write about. Unless stated otherwise, our editorial content is not influenced by advertisers or affiliate partnerships. This disclosure is provided in accordance with the Federal Trade Commission’s 16 CFR § 255.5: Guides Concerning the Use of Endorsements and Testimonials in Advertising.”

**Opt of Cookies**

If you do not want the benefits of cookies, there is a simple procedure that allows you to deny or accept this feature. In order to “opt out” of the benefits of cookies, you may manually delete your cookies by following the instructions contained in the Help section of your browser.

To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Governmental Agencies**

As and when required by law, we may disclose your information with governmental agencies in response to a subpoena, court order or other legal process.

**Right to Transfer Data**

Should the Company choose to sell or transfer business assets, it is possible that the information we possess may be transferred as part of that transaction. The Company may decide to retain a copy of the information post sale or transfer. With respect to your personal information; should a combination or acquisition occur, the newly combined or acquiring entity will be requested to follow this privacy policy and inform users of the legal ownership changes. This request is encouraged, but cannot be guaranteed.

**Partner Websites**

MilitaryBenefits.info will from time to time offer external links to other third party websites. These sites have their own terms of use and privacy and security policies. Should you visit one of these sites, you are encouraged to review the governing policies for that particular site.

**Notification of Policy Changes**

Company reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time. It is your obligation as a consumer to periodically check the Privacy Policy in effect by visiting the site and noting the effective date of the policy.

**Limitation of Liability**

By utilizing this website you UNDERSTAND and AGREE that ANY dispute as to the terms or application of this PRIVACY POLICY is subject to the Terms of Use associated with this website and the PRIVACY POLICY herein. This includes all limitations on damages and arbitration of disputes. You also agree that COMPANY’S liability for any breach of this privacy policy shall be limited to the value of the transactions or services provided to you through the use of this website to the extent that such claim in not otherwise barred through the sites TERMS AND CONDITIONS.

**Disclaimer**

This is a private website that is NOT affiliated with the U.S. government, U.S. Armed Forces or Department of Veteran Affairs. U.S. government agencies have not reviewed this information. This site contains information about GI Bill benefits, VA loans, news and services for military veterans and is not connected with any government agency. If you would like to find more information about benefits offered by Veteran Affairs, visit the official site for veterans benefits at [Veterans Affairs](http://www.va.gov/ "Veteran Affairs Official Site").

GI Bill® is a registered trademark of the U.S. Department of Veterans Affairs (VA). More information about education benefits offered by VA is available at the official U.S. government Web site at http://www.benefits.va.gov/gibill.

The appearance of U.S. Department of Defense (DoD) visual information does not imply or constitute DoD endorsement.

**Contact Information**

We can be contacted by emailing us at info at MilitaryBenefits.info or by mail at:

MilitaryBenefits.info  
17853 Santiago Blvd  
#107-261  
Villa Park, CA 92861

PLEASE NOTE: PERIODIC CHANGES ARE MADE TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY. PLEASE CHECK REGULARLY FOR UPDATES
